Sebastian Gołąb

Phone:

+48 886 165 556

Email:

sebagolab97@gmail .com

Date of birth:

02-08-1997

City:

Wadowice

ABOUT ME

I works as a programmer since 2017, I specialize in as frontend developer who makes new projects and advances existing ones. I am independent but also I good feel in team work where together we can develop our competencies.

I am person who not only creates code, but also engages in the full scope of the design process. I will be happy to share my experience and knowledge to create unique solutions together.

EXPERIENCE

1. Web Developer, Intermania Wadowice - from 2017 to 10 may 2022

In Intermania i made many projects in Wordpress, every website was maked on template which i design in figma and wrote from zero. I participated in every website process from talking with clients to final product.

2. Frontend Developer, Home.pl S.A. - from 10 may 2022 to now

At Home.pl I work as frontend developer in team who work on one large ecommerce project, we make new solutions, develop our project in terms of performance and fix bugs. I cooperate with UX and UI designers and business teams to make best product for our clients.

EDUCATION

CKZiU number 2 in Wadowice, IT profile — from 2013 to 2017

PORTFOLIO

https://sebastiangolab.pl/

SKILLS - TOOLS AND TECHNOLOGIES

HTML5, CSS3, Javascript ES6+, TypeScript, React, React Native, Gatsby, Next.js, Redux, REST API, Webpack, Styled Components, Sass, Bootstrap, Headless CMS, GraphQL, Wordpress, Prestashop, Jest, GIT, GSAP, MySQL, Figma, Spline

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Working in Scrum, SEO, AdWords, WCAG, designing website templates in figma, ability to manage social media channels, working with databases,

hosting support, ability to work in a team, experience in creating new projects from scratch

LANGUAGES

Polish, English (A2)

I consent to the processing of my personal data for the purpose of recruiting for the position I am applying for.